<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<CharInfos>
  <DetailedInfo>
    <!--휴먼 남자-->
    <Hm>Humans boast the longest history on Rohan Continent as the initial race. Ruled by hereditary monarchy, their nation Del Lagos was erected with capital Einhoren at the center. Possessing the largest population and strongest power, Humans serve as the continental benchmark.  Humans are predisposed to fight as a leader, and can choose between evolving into Defender or Guardian.  Defenders, brute of a soldier with strengthened defense, can cast stun spells and excel in ranged attacks.  Guardians boast refined attack skills and can even increase the amount of damage with their attacks.</Hm>
    <!--휴먼 여자-->
    <Hw>Humans boast the longest history on Rohan Continent as the initial race. Ruled by hereditary monarchy, their nation Del Lagos was erected with capital Einhoren at the center. Possessing the largest population and strongest power, Humans serve as the continental benchmark.  Humans are predisposed to fight as a leader, and can choose between evolving into Defender or Guardian.  Defenders, brute of a soldier with strengthened defense, can cast stun spells and excel in ranged attacks.  Guardians boast refined attack skills and can even increase the amount of damage with their attacks.</Hw>
    <!--엘프 남자-->
    <Em>The second race to become residents of Rohan are the beautiful Elves created by Marea. After having lost their first capital Regen to monsters, their civilization is being developed in Vena, their second capital. With Magic Academy located in Via Marea, the Elf nation, active magic research was being conducted surpassing other cities, the academy was fashioned into a magic training facility in preparation for war. Elves prize mental training over physical aspects and aptly employ magic on healing wounds and altruistic activities as advocates of peace.  Elves can evolve into Priests or Templars, with specializing in healing and protection using a range of powerful magic spells and Templars capable of both magical and physical attacks. But their healing powers are keen as well.</Em>
    <!--엘프 여자-->
    <Ew>The second race to become residents of Rohan are the beautiful Elves created by Marea. After having lost their first capital Regen to monsters, their civilization is being developed in Vena, their second capital. With Magic Academy located in Via Marea, the Elf nation, active magic research was being conducted surpassing other cities, the academy was fashioned into a magic training facility in preparation for war. Elves prize mental training over physical aspects and aptly employ magic on healing wounds and altruistic activities as advocates of peace.  Elves can evolve into Priests or Templars, with specializing in healing and protection using a range of powerful magic spells and Templars capable of both magical and physical attacks. But their healing powers are keen as well.</Ew>
    <!--하프엘프 남자-->
    <HEm>Active diplomacy between Humans and Elves followed the demise of the main god and destruction of the dragons resulting in the birth of the half-blood race evolved, known as the Half Elf. They are naturally intuitive of the forest enabling them to be experts in the use of bows and arrows.  Endowed with strengths and stability of Humans, combined with agility and sensibility inherited from Elves, they possess the most competent ranged offense on the Rohan continent. Job change can evolve them into Scouts or Rangers. Scouts are masters of multi-targeting with their bows (and magic), they often choose to fight all enemies at once rather than one at a time.  Rangers are well versed on the crossbow, Rangers dominate their opponents with swift and precise arrow and dagger attacks.</HEm>
    <!--하프엘프 여자-->
    <HEw>Active diplomacy between Humans and Elves followed the demise of the main god and destruction of the dragons resulting in the birth of the half-blood race evolved, known as the Half Elf. They are naturally intuitive of the forest enabling them to be experts in the use of bows and arrows.  Endowed with strengths and stability of Humans, combined with agility and sensibility inherited from Elves, they possess the most competent ranged offense on the Rohan continent. Job change can evolve them into Scouts or Rangers. Scouts are masters of multi-targeting with their bows (and magic), they often choose to fight all enemies at once rather than one at a time.  Rangers are well versed on the crossbow, Rangers dominate their opponents with swift and precise arrow and dagger attacks.</HEw>
    <!--단 남자-->
    <Dm>Kraute Del Lagos, pursued by human troops, fled to an island in the North with supporters, which became the founding fathers of the Dhan race.   Their onerous background drove the young Dhans to master the ways of the assassin out of a sense of duty for personal survival and enemy disposal.  Remote from the continent, they possess an entirely disparate culture from that of the mainland, producing unique alien weaponry.  They worship main god Ohn and Edoneh instead of the lower gods. Dhans can acquire experience by killing other players rather than completing quests if they choose.  The two evolving choices are Avengers and Predators.  Avengers can achieve invisibility and dismember opponents with no warning. Predators are quick, and deal blows so swiftly that anyone within striking distance may not even be able to take a single swing before death.</Dm>
    <!--단 여자-->
    <Dw>Kraute Del Lagos, pursued by human troops, fled to an island in the North with supporters, which became the founding fathers of the Dhan race.   Their onerous background drove the young Dhans to master the ways of the assassin out of a sense of duty for personal survival and enemy disposal.  Remote from the continent, they possess an entirely disparate culture from that of the mainland, producing unique alien weaponry.  They worship main god Ohn and Edoneh instead of the lower gods. Dhans can acquire experience by killing other players rather than completing quests if they choose.  The two evolving choices are Avengers and Predators.  Avengers can achieve invisibility and dismember opponents with no warning. Predators are quick, and deal blows so swiftly that anyone within striking distance may not even be able to take a single swing before death.</Dw>
    <!--데칸 남자-->
    <DKm>Unlike other races who were created by main god Ohn, Dekans are descendents of Blue Dragon Armenes, which their nation is named after.  Inhabiting the North, with capital Rev'Deca at the center, are profoundly proud of their provenance as dragon's descendents, and despise other races created by the lower gods.  Dragon Fighters defy nature, born with the nascent ability to transform from humanoid to a fiercely violent dragon!  Dragon Knights evolve more quickly in the form of dragon rather than humanoid, and employ a unique bloodsucking skill to weaken opponents.  Dragon Sages are  specialized hunters that can attack large areas at once. Pray you do not cross them underwater.</DKm>
    <!--데칸 여자-->
    <DKw>Unlike other races who were created by main god Ohn, Dekans are descendents of Blue Dragon Armenes, which their nation is named after.  Inhabiting the North, with capital Rev'Deca at the center, are profoundly proud of their provenance as dragon's descendents, and despise other races created by the lower gods.  Dragon Fighters defy nature, born with the nascent ability to transform from humanoid to a fiercely violent dragon!  Dragon Knights evolve more quickly in the form of dragon rather than humanoid, and employ a unique bloodsucking skill to weaken opponents.  Dragon Sages are  specialized hunters that can attack large areas at once. Pray you do not cross them underwater.</DKw>
    <!--다크엘프 남자-->
    <DEm>Dark Elves are cultured, but their aristocratic disposition and implicit disdaining appearance cause tension with other races.  Their capital, Montt, is located in Ignis at the southern tip of the Rohan Continent.  Presumably they live by decorum but secretly harbor ulterior motives.  The mysterious Dark Elven Mages employ strong magical powers to weaken and dispatch their enemies. Warlock Thrives in group battles, they seemingly are able to weaken opponents before the fighting even starts.  Wizard Expert hunters, they employ powerful area spells to fight off multiple opponents simultaneously.</DEm>
    <!--다크엘프 여자-->
    <DEw>Dark Elves are cultured, but their aristocratic disposition and implicit disdaining appearance cause tension with other races.  Their capital, Montt, is located in Ignis at the southern tip of the Rohan Continent.  Presumably they live by decorum but secretly harbor ulterior motives.  The mysterious Dark Elven Mages employ strong magical powers to weaken and dispatch their enemies. Warlock Thrives in group battles, they seemingly are able to weaken opponents before the fighting even starts.  Wizard Expert hunters, they employ powerful area spells to fight off multiple opponents simultaneously.</DEw>
    <!--자이언트 남자-->
    <Gm>A race created by Earth God Gail, they dwell in Draht, a country of arctic terrain, with Etton as their capital. The Giant race is more agile than they appear. Giants underwent extensive training in a warrior guild as a means to secure their town. Endowed with deep pride and a profound sense of fraternity, they show no mercy to enemies -- the brutal Savages and Berserkers they've trained to become.  
Warriors use their size to their advantage while remaining agile.  Berserker Specializing in PVP combat, wide-ranged skills enable these Giants to live up to their brutal names as Berserkers.  Savages provide Buffs to allies and Debuffs to enemies inside Totem Castles, ideal in party play with their wide-ranged attacks and party buffs.</Gm>
    <!--자이언트 여자-->
    <Gw>A race created by Earth God Gail, they dwell in Draht, a country of arctic terrain, with Etton as their capital. The Giant race is more agile than they appear. Giants underwent extensive training in a warrior guild as a means to secure their town. Endowed with deep pride and a profound sense of fraternity, they show no mercy to enemies -- the brutal Savages and Berserkers they've trained to become.  
Warriors use their size to their advantage while remaining agile.  Berserker Specializing in PVP combat, wide-ranged skills enable these Giants to live up to their brutal names as Berserkers.  Savages provide Buffs to allies and Debuffs to enemies inside Totem Castles, ideal in party play with their wide-ranged attacks and party buffs.</Gw>
  </DetailedInfo>
</CharInfos>